optimizerx.com 2011-02-19

# Prescription Coupons, Savings and Support Offers - OPTIMIZERx - Privacy Statement

**Internet Privacy Policy**

OPTIMIZERx and its participating sponsors recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of information we may collect from our online visitors. To this end, we are committed to using our best efforts to respect the privacy of our online visitors. It is our intent to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using information received from and about you with your reasonable expectations of privacy. The following is the way we handle information learned about you from your visit to our Web site. 

**Collective Data**

OPTIMIZERx deposits certain bits of information called cookies in a visitor’s computer. Cookies are sent back only to the Web site that deposited them when a visitor returns to that site. Cookies can tell us how and when pages in a Web site are visited and by how many people. This technology does not collect personal identifiable information; the information collected is in an aggregate, non identifiable form. With the information we can learn through this technology, we hope to improve our site. 

**Personally Identifiable Information (PII)**

OPTIMIZERx collects personally identifiable information (PII), such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, and the like, only when voluntarily provided by a Web site visitor and member. We use the Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to respond to your questions, provide you the specific services you select, send you emails about Web site maintenance and updates, and inform you of significant changes to this Privacy Policy. If required, this information may be used to marketing partners whose offer(s) you have selected to receive in order for them to send you those offer(s) or information via electronic delivery, telemarketing and direct mail. Please note, these companies are independent third parties over which OPTIMIZERx exercises no control. Therefore, we are not liable for, their conduct, actions, omissions, or information handling or dissemination practices.

**Links to Other Sites**

As a resource to our visitors, OPTIMIZERx provides links to other Web sites. We try to carefully choose Web sites we believe are useful and meet our high standards. However, because Web sites can change so quickly, we can’t guarantee the standards of every Web site link we provide or be responsible for the content of non-OPTIMIZERx sites.

**Newsletters & Emails to You**

At registration and at various times, as you use OPTIMIZERx, you will be given the option of receiving recurring informational/promotional newsletters via email from OPTIMIZERx and/or directly from third parties. These emails will not contain Personal Health Information. At the time you sign up for our email newsletters or any time thereafter, you can choose to Opt-In to receiving additional promotional emails from OPTIMIZERx. In order to subscribe to OPTIMIZERx Newsletters via email, we need your contact information, such as name and email address. You can unsubscribe from the newsletters by simply clicking on the ’unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of any email newsletter. An email to our automated unsubscribe service will be created on your computer. Click the ’send’ button. You will then be unsubscribed from that newsletter within two to three business days.

**Third-party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies are independent third parties over which OPTIMIZERx exercises no control. OPTIMIZERx is not responsible for, and will not be liable for, their conduct, actions, omissions, or information handling or dissemination practices.

**Security**

The OPTIMIZERx Web Site has security measures in place intended to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. Our hardware infrastructure is housed in a controlled access facility that restricts access to authorized individuals with positive identification. Our network access to the infrastructure is protected by a firewall protection system. Member information is backed up on a periodic basis to protect against accidental loss. However, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and OPTIMIZERx will not be intercepted by others and that information stored on our servers will be free from unauthorized access. While we have taken reasonable precautions to protect this information, you should always use discretion in what information you send to us and not expect that such information will be absolutely free from intrusion. The confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from OPTIMIZERx Web Site or via e-mail cannot be and is not guaranteed. Accordingly, OPTIMIZERx is not responsible for the security of information transmitted via the Internet.

**Children**

In general, OPTIMIZERx services and websites are not directed at children and are designed for individuals who are 18 years of age or older. We will not request or knowingly collect information from an individual under 13 years of age. Disclosures OPTIMIZERx information about you and your use of the OPTIMIZERx Web Site and the OPTIMIZERx Services if OPTIMIZERx believes such disclosure is reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with the law or legal process; (ii) to protect or defend the rights or property of OPTIMIZERx or others; (iii) to enforce the OPTIMIZERx Terms and Conditions or this Privacy Policy; and (iv) to respond to claims that the content(s) of a communication violates the rights of another. We employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. These agents have access to member information as needed to perform their functions for OPTIMIZERx. While OPTIMIZERx may undertake efforts to see that any third party to which OPTIMIZERx shares or otherwise discloses a member or user’s information is under a contractual obligation to use the information solely for the purposes for which the data was disclosed, such third parties are independent third parties over which OPTIMIZERx exercises no control. OPTIMIZERx is not responsible for, and will not be liable for, their conduct, actions, omissions, or information handling or dissemination practices.

**Market Research**

You may choose to participate in market research activities through OPTIMIZERx, including health panels and surveys. When participating in such activities, we may ask you to submit personal information. We may combine the personal information you provide to us with research tools and information from other sources, including prescription information. We use this information to perform research, and to prepare reports and analyses for our clients. Our reports and analyses to clients are made only on an anonymous basis. Our clients never see any single individual’s personal information and we will not use the personal information you provided during market research activities to advertise, promote, or market goods or services to you. Any changes to this privacy policy will be communicated promptly on this page.

Effective: July 2007
